Guide to the New York State College of Veterinary Medicine Office of the Dean records, 1932 -1950
New York State College of Veterinary Medicine Office of the Dean records, 1932-1950
- Series IV. 1940-1942
  - Dykstra, R.R., ca. 1940 - 1942 (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - D Misc., ca. 1940 - 1942 (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Eastman, E.R., ca. 1940 - 1942 (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - Evans, W.M., ca. 1940 - 1942 (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - E Misc., ca. 1940 - 1942 (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - F Misc., ca. 1940 - 1942 (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - Faculty, ca. 1940 - 1942 (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - Fanslau, Chas E., ca. 1940 - 1942 (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - Faulder, E.T., ca. 1940 - 1942 (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - Fehr, F.F., ca. 1940 - 1942 (Box 7, Folder 32)
  - Feldman, W.H., ca. 1940 - 1942 (Box 7, Folder 33)
  - Field, H.L., ca. 1940 - 1942 (Box 7, Folder 34)
  - Fincher, M.G., ca. 1940 - 1942 (Box 7, Folder 35)
  - Flynn, J.E., ca. 1940 - 1942 (Box 7, Folder 36)
  - Foster, E.S., ca. 1940 - 1942 (Box 7, Folder 37)
  - Frank, Geo S., ca. 1940 - 1942 (Box 7, Folder 38)
  - Fred, E.B., ca. 1940 - 1942 (Box 7, Folder 39)
  - Frick, E.J., ca. 1940 - 1942 (Box 7, Folder 40)
  - Frost, J.N., ca. 1940 - 1942 (Box 7, Folder 41)
  - Fuller, H.K., ca. 1940 - 1942 (Box 7, Folder 42)
  - G Misc., ca. 1940 - 1942 (Box 7, Folder 43)
  - Gannett, R.W., ca. 1940 - 1942 (Box 7, Folder 44)
  - Gibson, H.H., ca. 1940 - 1942 (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - Gifford, Rebecca G., ca. 1940 - 1942 (Box 7, Folder 45)
  - Gilman, H.S., ca. 1940 - 1942 (Box 7, Folder 46)
  - Giltner, Ward, ca. 1940 - 1942 (Box 7, Folder 47)
  - Gordon, Ruth, ca. 1940 - 1942 (Box 7, Folder 48)
  - Goss, L.J., ca. 1940 - 1942 (Box 7, Folder 49)
  - Goss, L.W., ca. 1940 - 1942 (Box 7, Folder 50)
  - Graham, E.K., ca. 1940 - 1942 (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - Graham, Robert, ca. 1940 - 1942 (Box 7, Folder 51)
  - Graves, Frank P., ca. 1940 - 1942 (Box 7, Folder 52)
  - H Misc. (Folder 1 of 2), ca. 1940 - 1942 (Box 7, Folder 53)
  - H Misc. (Folder 2 of 2), ca. 1940 - 1942 (Box 7, Folder 54)
  - Hallman, E.T., ca. 1940 - 1942 (Box 7, Folder 55)
  - Hardenbergh, J.G., ca. 1940 - 1942 (Box 7, Folder 56)
  - Haring, C.M., ca. 1940 - 1942 (Box 7, Folder 57)
  - Haupin, G.D., ca. 1940 - 1942 (Box 7, Folder 58)
  - Heads of Depts, ca. 1940 - 1942 (Box 7, Folder 59)
  - Heisler, Charles B., ca. 1940 - 1942 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Hendershott, R.A., ca. 1940 - 1942 (Box 19, Folder 17)
  - Hertel, J.P., ca. 1940 - 1942 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Heylar, F.G., ca. 1940 - 1942 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Hilbert, K.F., ca. 1940 - 1942 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Holford, F.D., ca. 1940 - 1942 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Holmes, F.B., ca. 1940 - 1942 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Hopper, Earle B., ca. 1940 - 1942 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Hotels, ca. 1940 - 1942 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Hucker, G.J., ca. 1940 - 1942 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Hurt, L.M., ca. 1940 - 1942 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Hutt, F.B., ca. 1940 - 1942 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - I Misc., ca. 1940 - 1942 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - J Misc., ca. 1940 - 1942 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Jakeman, H.W., ca. 1940 - 1942 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Johnson, S.D., ca. 1940 - 1942 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Jordan, John Jr., ca. 1940 - 1942 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - K Misc., ca. 1940 - 1942 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Kahl, Paul L., ca. 1940 - 1942 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - King, A.C., ca. 1940 - 1942 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Kinkeldey, Otto, ca. 1940 - 1942 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Kinney, James R., ca. 1940 - 1942 (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Kelser, R.A., ca. 1940 - 1942 (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Kent, L.C., ca. 1940 - 1942 (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - Knapp, H.B., ca. 1940 - 1942 (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - L Misc., ca. 1940 - 1942 (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - Lacroix, J.V., ca. 1940 - 1942 (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - Lederle Laboratories, ca. 1940 - 1942 (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - Lehn & Fink Products Corp., ca. 1940 - 1942 (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - Leonard, H.B., ca. 1940 - 1942 (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - Levine, P.P., ca. 1940 - 1942 (Box 8, Folder 30)
  - Loomis, Milton E., ca. 1940 - 1942 (Box 19, Folder 18)
  - McAuliff, J.L., ca. 1940 - 1942 (Box 8, Folder 31)
  - McClelland, F.E., ca. 1940 - 1942 (Box 8, Folder 32)
  - McGilvray, C.D., ca. 1940 - 1942 (Box 8, Folder 33)
  - McKim, O.E., ca. 1940 - 1942 (Box 8, Folder 34)
  - Mangan, C. Everts, ca. 1940 - 1942 (Box 8, Folder 35)
  - Marsteller, R.P., ca. 1940 - 1942 (Box 8, Folder 36)
  - Matthews, James, E., ca. 1940 - 1942 (Box 8, Folder 37)
  - Maynard, L.A., ca. 1940 - 1942 (Box 8, Folder 38)
  - Mayo, N.S., ca. 1940 - 1942 (Box 8, Folder 39)
  - Mead, James M., ca. 1940 - 1942 (Box 8, Folder 40)
  - Meek, H.B., ca. 1940 - 1942 (Box 8, Folder 41)
  - Meigs, Robert B., ca. 1940 - 1942 (Box 19, Folder 19)
  - Merck & Co., ca. 1940 - 1942 (Box 8, Folder 42)
  - Merillat, L.A., ca. 1940 - 1942 (Box 8, Folder 43)
  - Merry, A.E., ca. 1940 - 1942 (Box 8, Folder 44)
  - Milks, H.J., ca. 1940 - 1942 (Box 8, Folder 45)
  - Millar, J.A.S., ca. 1940 - 1942 (Box 8, Folder 46)
  - Miller, A.W., ca. 1940 - 1942 (Box 8, Folder 47)
  - Miller, J. Hillis, ca. 1940 - 1942 (Box 8, Folder 48)
  - Miller, M.E., ca. 1940 - 1942 (Box 8, Folder 49)
  - Mohler, John R., ca. 1940 - 1942 (Box 8, Folder 50)
  - Monroe, B.S., ca. 1940 - 1942 (Box 8, Folder 51)
  - Moore, E.V., ca. 1940 - 1942 (Box 8, Folder 52)
  - Morris, Evan J., ca. 1940 - 1942 (Box 8, Folder 53)
  - Morris, Fred B., ca. 1940 - 1942 (Box 8, Folder 54)
  - Morris, Mark L., ca. 1940 - 1942 (Box 19, Folder 20)
  - Morrison, F.B., ca. 1940 - 1942 (Box 8, Folder 55)
  - Murray, Charles, ca. 1940 - 1942 (Box 8, Folder 56)
  - Ma Misc., ca. 1940 - 1942 (Box 8, Folder 57)
  - Mc, ca. 1940 - 1942 (Box 8, Folder 58)
  - Me, ca. 1940 - 1942 (Box 8, Folder 59)
  - Mi, ca. 1940 - 1942 (Box 8, Folder 60)
  - Mu, ca. 1940 - 1942 (Box 8, Folder 61)
  - Nevitt, John, ca. 1940 - 1942 (Box 8, Folder 62)
  - Newman, W.S., ca. 1940 - 1942 (Box 8, Folder 63)
  - Newsom., I.E., ca. 1940 - 1942 (Box 8, Folder 64)
  - Norden Laboratories, ca. 1940 - 1942 (Box 8, Folder 65)
  - Noyes, H.V., ca. 1940 - 1942 (Box 8, Folder 66)
  - Nutrition Research Laboratories Inc., ca. 1940 - 1942 (Box 8, Folder 67)
  - N Misc., ca. 1940 - 1942 (Box 8, Folder 68)
  - Olafson, Peter, ca. 1940 - 1942 (Box 8, Folder 69)
  - Olson, Carl Jr., ca. 1940 - 1942 (Box 8, Folder 70)
  - Oppenheimer, R.B., ca. 1940 - 1942 (Box 8, Folder 71)
  - O Misc., ca. 1940 - 1942 (Box 8, Folder 72)
  - Parker, L.L., ca. 1940 - 1942 (Box 8, Folder 73)
  - Patterson, F.D., ca. 1940 - 1942 (Box 8, Folder 74)
  - Phi Kappa Phi, ca. 1940 - 1942 (Box 8, Folder 75)
  - Phillips, Maud, ca. 1940 - 1942 (Box 19, Folder 21)
  - Pitman Moore Co., ca. 1940 - 1942 (Box 8, Folder 76)
  - Procurement and Assignment Services, ca. 1940 - 1942 (Box 8, Folder 77)
  - Pa - Pe, ca. 1940 - 1942 (Box 8, Folder 78)
  - Pe - Pl, ca. 1940 - 1942 (Box 8, Folder 79)
  - Reagan, J.J. (Folder 1 of 2), ca. 1940 - 1942 (Box 8, Folder 80)
  - Reagan, J.J. (Folder 2 of 2), ca. 1940 - 1942 (Box 8, Folder 81)
  - Rivers, Thomas M., ca. 1940 - 1942 (Box 8, Folder 82)
  - Rogalsky, George F., ca. 1940 - 1942 (Box 8, Folder 83)
  - Ra - Rd, ca. 1940 - 1942 (Box 8, Folder 84)
  - Re - Rl, ca. 1940 - 1942 (Box 8, Folder 85)
  - Rm - Rz, ca. 1940 - 1942 (Box 8, Folder 86)
  - Rm - Rz, ca. 1940 - 1942 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Sabine, G.H., ca. 1940 - 1942 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Sandholzer, L.A., ca. 1940 - 1942 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Sc., ca. 1940 - 1942 (Box 19, Folder 22)
  - Schlotthauer, C.F., ca. 1940 - 1942 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Schmidt, A.W., ca. 1940 - 1942 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Schnelle, G.B., ca. 1940 - 1942 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Schoening H.W., ca. 1940 - 1942 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Schroeder, C.R., ca. 1940 - 1942 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Schroeder, E.F., ca. 1940 - 1942 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Sherman, J.M., ca. 1940 - 1942 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Simms, B.T., ca. 1940 - 1942 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Simpson, A.D., ca. 1940 - 1942 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Stephenson, H.C., ca. 1940 - 1942 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Stubbs, E.L., ca. 1940 - 1942 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Sunderville, E., ca. 1940 - 1942 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Syverton, J.T., ca. 1940 - 1942 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Sa - Sh, ca. 1940 - 1942 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Si - Sl, ca. 1940 - 1942 (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Sm - Sp, ca. 1940 - 1942 (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - St, ca. 1940 - 1942 (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - Su, ca. 1940 - 1942 (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - Tenbroeck, Carl, ca. 1940 - 1942 (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - Thorning, William, ca. 1940 - 1942 (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - Trousdale, J.B., ca. 1940 - 1942 (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - Ta - Tl, ca. 1940 - 1942 (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - Tm - Tz, ca. 1940 - 1942 (Box 9, Folder 26)
  - Udall, D.H., ca. 1940 - 1942 (Box 9, Folder 27)
  - U Misc., ca. 1940 - 1942 (Box 9, Folder 28)
  - Van Auken, G.L., ca. 1940 - 1942 (Box 9, Folder 29)
  - V Misc., ca. 1940 - 1942 (Box 9, Folder 30)
  - Way, Cassius, ca. 1940 - 1942 (Box 9, Folder 31)
  - Weatherlow, H.E., ca. 1940 - 1942 (Box 9, Folder 32)
  - Weber, A.S., ca. 1940 - 1942 (Box 9, Folder 33)
  - Wegner, E.E., ca. 1940 - 1942 (Box 19, Folder 23)
  - Wheeler, R.H., ca. 1940 - 1942 (Box 9, Folder 34)
  - Wight, A.E., ca. 1940 - 1942 (Box 9, Folder 35)
  - Will Corporation, ca. 1940 - 1942 (Box 9, Folder 36)
  - Williams, H.H., ca. 1940 - 1942 (Box 9, Folder 37)
  - Wilson, L.A., ca. 1940 - 1942 (Box 9, Folder 38)
  - Wa - Wd, ca. 1940 - 1942 (Box 9, Folder 39)
  - We - Wg, ca. 1940 - 1942 (Box 9, Folder 40)
  - Wh - Wn, ca. 1940 - 1942 (Box 9, Folder 41)
  - Wo - Wz, ca. 1940 - 1942 (Box 9, Folder 42)
  - Zeissig, A, ca. 1940 - 1942 (Box 9, Folder 43)
  - Zepp, C.P., ca. 1940 - 1942 (Box 9, Folder 44)
  - XYZ Misc., ca. 1940 - 1942 (Box 9, Folder 45)
- Series V. 1942-1943
  - Admissions, ca. 1942 - 1944 (Box 9, Folder 46)
  - Adams, Bristow, ca. 1942 - 1943 (Box 9, Folder 47)
  - A, ca. 1942 - 1943 (Box 9, Folder 48)
  - Ba, ca. 1942 - 1943 (Box 9, Folder 49)
  - Bo, ca. 1942 - 1943 (Box 9, Folder 50)
  - C, ca. 1942 - 1943 (Box 9, Folder 51)
  - Da, ca. 1942 - 1943 (Box 9, Folder 52)
  - Do, ca. 1942 - 1943 (Box 9, Folder 53)
  - E, ca. 1942 - 1943 (Box 9, Folder 54)
  - Fa, ca. 1942 - 1943 (Box 9, Folder 55)
  - Fo, ca. 1942 - 1943 (Box 9, Folder 56)
  - Ga, ca. 1942 - 1943 (Box 9, Folder 57)
  - Go, ca. 1942 - 1943 (Box 9, Folder 58)
  - Ha, ca. 1942 - 1943 (Box 9, Folder 59)
  - Ho, ca. 1942 - 1943 (Box 9, Folder 60)
  - J, ca. 1942 - 1943 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Ka, ca. 1942 - 1943 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - La, ca. 1942 - 1943 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Li, ca. 1942 - 1943 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Mac & Mc, ca. 1942 - 1943 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Ma, ca. 1942 - 1943 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Me, ca. 1942 - 1943 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Mo, ca. 1942 - 1943 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - N, ca. 1942 - 1943 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - O, ca. 1942 - 1943 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - P, ca. 1942 - 1943 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Ph, ca. 1942 - 1943 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Ra, ca. 1942 - 1943 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Ro, ca. 1942 - 1943 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Sa, ca. 1942 - 1943 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Se, ca. 1942 - 1943 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - So, ca. 1942 - 1943 (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - T, ca. 1942 - 1943 (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - U, ca. 1942 - 1943 (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - V, ca. 1942 - 1943 (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - Wa, ca. 1942 - 1943 (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - Wi, ca. 1942 - 1943 (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - XYZ, ca. 1942 - 1944 (Box 10, Folder 23)
- Series VI. 1943-1947
  - Aa - Ar, ca. 1943 - 1947 (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - Admissions 1948 (Box 10, Folder 25)
  - Agriculture, College of, ca. 1943 - 1947 (Box 10, Folder 26)
  - Alpha Psi, ca. 1943 - 1947 (Box 10, Folder 27)
  - Alpha Sigma Phi, ca. 1943 - 1947 (Box 10, Folder 28)
  - Anatomy, ca. 1943 - 1947 (Box 10, Folder 29)
  - Announcements, ca. 1943 - 1947 (Box 10, Folder 30)
  - Annual Report, ca. 1943 - 1947 (Box 10, Folder 31)
  - Artificial Insemination, ca. 1943 - 1947 (Box 10, Folder 32)
  - Association of American Veterinary Deans, ca. 1943 - 1947 (Box 10, Folder 33)
  - A.V.M.A. Council on Education, ca. 1945 - 1947 (Box 10, Folder 34)
  - A.V.M.A. Council on Education, ca. 1945 - 1947 (Box 10, Folder 35)
  - A.V.M.A., ca. 1945 - 1947 (Box 10, Folder 36)
  - A.V.M.A., ca. 1945 - 1947 (Box 10, Folder 37)
  - A.V.M.A. Research Council, ca. 1946 - 1947 (Box 10, Folder 38)
  - Baker, D.W., ca. 1943 - 1947 (Box 10, Folder 39)
  - Bang's Disease, ca. 1943 - 1947 (Box 10, Folder 40)
  - The Borden Company Foundation, ca. 1945 - 1947 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Boy Scouts, ca. 1945 - 1947 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Boys in Service, ca. 1943 - 1947 (Box 19, Folder 24)
  - Budget, ca. 1943 - 1947 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Buildings, ca. 1943 - 1947 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Bureau of Animal Industry, ca. 1943 - 1947 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - B, ca. 1943 - 1947 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - California, University of, ca. 1943 - 1947 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Civil Service (Federal of State), ca. 1943 - 1947 (Box 19, Folder 25)
  - Committee on Animal Health, ca. 1943 - 1947 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Committee on Standard Methods for Dairy Products, ca. 1943 - 1947 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Committee on Student Conduct, ca. 1943 - 1947 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Committees, ca. 1943 - 1947 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Conference, ca. 1943 - 1947 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Conference of Research Workers in Animal Disease in North America, ca. 1943 - 1947 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - (Prior to Jan. 1949) Council for the N.Y.S.V.C, ca. 1943 - 1947 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Cu - Cz, ca. 1943 - 1947 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Danforth Foundation, ca. 1943 - 1947 (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Danks, A.G., ca. 1943 - 1947 (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Data - N.Y.S. Veterinary College, ca. 1943 - 1947 (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Day, Edmund Ezra, ca. 1943 - 1947 (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - Deceased 1948 Xmas Letters, ca. 1948 (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - DeCamp, C.E.0, ca. 1943 - 1947 (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - Diseases, ca. 1943 - 1947 (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - Dukes, H.H., ca. 1943 - 1947 (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - D, ca. 1943 - 1947 (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - Employment, ca. 1943 - 1947 (Box 11, Folder 25)
  - Ea - En, ca. 1943 - 1947 (Box 11, Folder 26)
  - Equipment, ca. 1943 - 1947 (Box 11, Folder 27)
  - Ethics, ca. 1943 - 1947 (Box 11, Folder 28)
  - Executive Committee - Board of Trustees, ca. 1943 - 1947 (Box 11, Folder 29)
  - Expense Accounts - A.V.M.A., ca. 1943 - 1947 (Box 11, Folder 30)
  - Faculty, ca. 1943 - 1947 (Box 11, Folder 31)
  - Farm Practice, ca. 1943 - 1947 (Box 11, Folder 32)
  - Field Laboratories, ca. 1943 - 1947 (Box 11, Folder 33)
  - Fire Equipment Protection etc., Inspection, ca. 1943 - 1947 (Box 11, Folder 34)
  - Foreign Inquiries, ca. 1943 - 1947 (Box 11, Folder 35)
  - Foreign Veterinary Schools, ca. 1943 - 1947 (Box 11, Folder 36)
  - Freshmen, ca. 1943 - 1947 (Box 11, Folder 37)
  - F, ca. 1943 - 1947 (Box 11, Folder 38)
  - Gage, S.H., ca. 1943 - 1947 (Box 11, Folder 39)
  - Georgia, Univ. of Athens, ca. 1943 - 1947 (Box 11, Folder 40)
  - Gilman, H.L., ca. 1943 - 1947 (Box 11, Folder 41)
  - Goss, L.J., ca. 1943 - 1947 (Box 11, Folder 42)
  - G, ca. 1943 - 1947 (Box 11, Folder 43)
  - Hagan, W.A., ca. 1943 - 1947 (Box 11, Folder 44)
  - Hagan, W.A. - Trips, ca. 1943 - 1947 (Box 11, Folder 45)
  - Hayden, C.E., ca. 1943 - 1947 (Box 11, Folder 46)
  - Hendershott, R.A., ca. 1943 - 1947 (Box 11, Folder 47)
  - Hilbert, K.F., ca. 1943 - 1947 (Box 11, Folder 48)
  - Holidays, ca. 1943 - 1947 (Box 11, Folder 49)
  - Horses and Horseshoeing, ca. 1943 - 1947 (Box 11, Folder 50)
  - Housing, ca. 1943 - 1947 (Box 19, Folder 26)
  - Howe, Ivan G., ca. 1943 - 1947 (Box 11, Folder 51)
  - Ha - Hl, ca. 1943 - 1947 (Box 11, Folder 52)
  - Hu - Hz, ca. 1943 - 1947 (Box 11, Folder 53)
  - Illinois, University of, ca. 1943 - 1947 (Box 11, Folder 54)
  - Ingmand, Eugene B., ca. 1943 - 1947 (Box 11, Folder 55)
  - Invitations, ca. 1943 - 1947 (Box 11, Folder 56)
  - Iowa State College, Ames, ca. 1943 - 1947 (Box 11, Folder 57)
  - Jakeman, H.W., ca. 1943 - 1947 (Box 11, Folder 58)
  - Jennnings, William E, ca. 1943 - 1947 (Box 19, Folder 27)
  - Jensen - Salsbury Laboratories, Inc., ca. 1943 - 1947 (Box 11, Folder 59)
  - Johnson, S.D., ca. 1943 - 1947 (Box 11, Folder 60)
  - Jordan, John, ca. 1943 - 1947 (Box 11, Folder 61)
  - J Misc., ca. 1943 - 1947 (Box 11, Folder 62)
  - Kelser, R.A., ca. 1943 - 1947 (Box 11, Folder 63)
  - Kent, L.C., ca. 1943 - 1947 (Box 11, Folder 64)
  - Kentucky, Univ. of, ca. 1943 - 1947 (Box 11, Folder 65)
  - King, A.C., ca. 1943 - 1947 (Box 11, Folder 66)
  - Kinkeldy, Otto, ca. 1943 - 1947 (Box 11, Folder 67)
  - Kinney, James R., ca. 1943 - 1947 (Box 11, Folder 68)
  - Klussendorf, R.C., ca. 1943 - 1947 (Box 11, Folder 69)
  - Knapp, H.B., ca. 1943 - 1947 (Box 11, Folder 70)
  - Ka - Kl, ca. 1943 - 1947 (Box 11, Folder 71)
  - Km - Kz, ca. 1943 - 1947 (Box 11, Folder 72)
  - Lacroix, J.V., ca. 1943 - 1947 (Box 11, Folder 73)
  - Lederle Laboratories, ca. 1943 - 1947 (Box 11, Folder 74)
  - Leonard, H.B., ca. 1943 - 1947 (Box 11, Folder 75)
  - Levine, P.P., ca. 1943 - 1947 (Box 19, Folder 28)
  - Libraries, ca. 1943 - 1947 (Box 19, Folder 29)
  - Library, ca. 1943 - 1947 (Box 11, Folder 76)
  - Le - Ll, ca. 1943 - 1947 (Box 11, Folder 77)
  - Lm - Lz, ca. 1943 - 1947 (Box 11, Folder 78)
  - Ma - Md, ca. 1943 - 1947 (Box 11, Folder 79)
  - Marstellar, R.P., ca. 1943 - 1947 (Box 11, Folder 80)
  - Mastitits Program, ca. 1943 - 1947 (Box 11, Folder 81)
  - Matthews, JAS, ca. 1943 - 1947 (Box 11, Folder 82)
  - Mayo, N.S., ca. 1943 - 1947 (Box 11, Folder 83)
  - McAuliff, J.L., ca. 1944 - 1947 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - McClelland, F.E., ca. 1944 - 1947 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - McGilvray, ca. 1944 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - McKim, O.E., ca. 1943 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Mc Misc., ca. 1943 - 1947 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Me, ca. 1943 - 1947 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Mead, Jas. M., ca. 1944 - 1946 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Medicine Department, ca. 1945 - 1947 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Medicines - Inquiries regarding, ca. 1943 - 1947 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Merck and Company, ca. 1944 - 1945 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Medical Society of the State of New York, ca. 1946 - 1948 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Merillat, L.A., ca. 1943 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Merry, A.E., ca. 1943 - 1947 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Mi - Ml, ca. 1943 - 1947 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Milks, H.J., ca. 1943 - 1947 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Miller, A.W., ca. 1943 - 1947 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Miller, J. Hillis, ca. 1943 - 1947 (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Millar, J.A.S., ca. 1943 - 1947 (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - Mo, ca. 1943 - 1947 (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - Mohler, J.R., ca. 1943 - 1947 (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - Moore, E.V., ca. 1943 - 1947 (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - Morris, Evan J., ca. 1943 - 1946 (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - Morris, Fred B., ca. 1943 - 1944 (Box 12, Folder 23)
  - Morris, M.L., ca. 1946 - 1947 (Box 12, Folder 24)
  - Morrison, F.B., ca. 1941 - 1945 (Box 12, Folder 25)
  - Mu - Mz, ca. 1943 - 1947 (Box 12, Folder 26)
  - Murphy, Dr. James M., ca. 1946 - 1947 (Box 12, Folder 27)
  - Murray, Charles, ca. 1943 (Box 12, Folder 28)
  - Myers, W.I., ca. 1945 - 1947 (Box 12, Folder 29)
  - Na - Nl, ca. 1943 - 1948 (Box 12, Folder 30)
  - National Research Council, ca. 1943 - 1947 (Box 12, Folder 31)
  - National Society for Medical Research, ca. 1943 - 1947 (Box 12, Folder 32)
  - Nevitt, John V., ca. 1943 - 1947 (Box 12, Folder 33)
  - Newman, W.S., ca. 1943 - 1947 (Box 12, Folder 34)
  - Newsome, I.E., ca. 1943 - 1947 (Box 12, Folder 35)
  - New York Academy of Sciences, ca. 1943 - 1947 (Box 12, Folder 36)
  - N.Y.S. Conference Board of Farm Organizations, ca. 1943 - 1947 (Box 12, Folder 37)
  - N.Y.S. Education Department, ca. 1943 - 1947 (Box 12, Folder 38)
  - New York State Health Department, ca. 1943 - 1947 (Box 12, Folder 39)
  - N.Y.S. Veterinary Medical Society, ca. 1943 - 1947 (Box 12, Folder 40)
  - N.Y. Zoological Society, ca. 1943 - 1947 (Box 12, Folder 41)
  - Norden Laboratories, ca. 1943 - 1947 (Box 12, Folder 42)
  - North American Veterinarian, ca. 1943 - 1947 (Box 12, Folder 43)
  - North Carolina, University of, ca. 1943 - 1947 (Box 12, Folder 44)
  - Nova Scotia, ca. 1943 - 1947 (Box 12, Folder 45)
  - Nutrition, ca. 1943 - 1947 (Box 12, Folder 46)
  - O Misc., ca. 1943 - 1947 (Box 12, Folder 47)
  - Ohio State University, ca. 1943 - 1947 (Box 12, Folder 48)
  - Olafson, Peter, ca. 1943 - 1947 (Box 12, Folder 49)
  - Olson, Carl, ca. 1943 - 1947 (Box 12, Folder 50)
  - Pa - Pd, ca. 1943 - 1947 (Box 12, Folder 51)
  - Papers, ca. 1943 - 1947 (Box 12, Folder 52)
  - Parasitology, ca. 1943 - 1947 (Box 12, Folder 53)
  - Parker, L.L., ca. 1943 - 1947 (Box 12, Folder 54)
  - Pathology, ca. 1943 - 1947 (Box 12, Folder 55)
  - Patterson, F.D., ca. 1943 - 1947 (Box 12, Folder 56)
  - Pe - Pl, ca. 1943 - 1947 (Box 12, Folder 57)
  - Pennsylvania, University of, ca. 1943 - 1947 (Box 12, Folder 58)
  - Phi Kappa Phi, ca. 1943 - 1947 (Box 12, Folder 59)
  - Phillips, Maud E., ca. 1943 - 1947 (Box 12, Folder 60)
  - Photographs, ca. 1943 - 1947 (Box 12, Folder 61)
  - Physiology, ca. 1943 - 1947 (Box 12, Folder 62)
  - Pitman-Moore Co., ca. 1943 - 1947 (Box 12, Folder 63)
  - Pm - Pz, ca. 1943 - 1947 (Box 12, Folder 64)
  - Positions Wanted, ca. 1943 - 1947 (Box 12, Folder 65)
  - Post-War Capital Projects, ca. 1943 - 1947 (Box 12, Folder 66)
  - Post-War Capital Projects, ca. 1943 - 1947 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Poultry, ca. 1943 - 1947 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Prizes, ca. 1943 - 1947 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Procurement and Assignment Service, ca. 1943 - 1947 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Publications, ca. 1943 - 1947 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Publicity, ca. 1943 - 1947 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Q Misc., ca. 1943 - 1947 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Ra - Rl, ca. 1943 - 1947 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Rabies, ca. 1943 - 1947 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Refresher Course, ca. 1943 - 1947 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Research, ca. 1943 - 1947 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Research and Development Board, ca. 1943 - 1947 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Rife, C.C., ca. 1943 - 1947 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Rm - Rz, ca. 1943 - 1947 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Rogalsky, G.F., ca. 1943 - 1947 (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Sa - Sc, ca. 1943 - 1947 (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Se -Sh, ca. 1943 - 1947 (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Sabine, G.H., ca. 1943 - 1947 (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - Sampson, Jesse, ca. 1943 - 1947 (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - W.B. Saunders and Co., ca. 1943 - 1947 (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - Schlotthauer, C.F., ca. 1943 - 1947 (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - Schmidt, A.W., ca. 1943 - 1947 (Box 13, Folder 22)
  - Schnelle, G.B., ca. 1943 - 1947 (Box 13, Folder 23)
  - Schoening, H.W., ca. 1943 - 1947 (Box 13, Folder 24)
  - Scholarships and Fellowships, ca. 1943 - 1947 (Box 13, Folder 25)
  - Schroeder, C.R., ca. 1943 - 1947 (Box 13, Folder 26)
  - Schroeder, E.F., ca. 1943 - 1947 (Box 13, Folder 27)
  - Secretary of University, ca. 1943 - 1947 (Box 13, Folder 28)
  - Seniors, ca. 1943 - 1947 (Box 13, Folder 29)
  - Sherman, J.M., ca. 1943 - 1947 (Box 13, Folder 30)
  - Si - Sl, ca. 1943 - 1947 (Box 13, Folder 31)
  - Sigma Xi, ca. 1943 - 1947 (Box 13, Folder 32)
  - Simms, B.T., ca. 1943 - 1947 (Box 13, Folder 33)
  - Simons, L.R., ca. 1943 - 1947 (Box 13, Folder 34)
  - Site and Landscape Specifications, ca. 1943 - 1947 (Box 13, Folder 35)
  - Sm - Sp, ca. 1943 - 1947 (Box 13, Folder 36)
  - Smith Misc., ca. 1943 - 1947 (Box 13, Folder 37)
  - Society of American Bacteriologists, ca. 1943 - 1947 (Box 13, Folder 38)
  - Speight, Harold E.B., ca. 1943 - 1947 (Box 13, Folder 39)
  - St, ca. 1943 - 1947 (Box 13, Folder 40)
  - State Boards, ca. 1943 - 1947 (Box 13, Folder 41)
  - Stephenson, H.C., ca. 1943 - 1947 (Box 13, Folder 42)
  - Su - Sz, ca. 1943 - 1947 (Box 13, Folder 43)
  - Surgery, ca. 1943 - 1947 (Box 13, Folder 44)
  - Swift and Company, ca. 1943 - 1947 (Box 13, Folder 45)
  - Swine, ca. 1943 - 1947 (Box 13, Folder 46)
  - Syverton, J.T., ca. 1943 - 1947 (Box 13, Folder 47)
  - Ta - Tl, ca. 1943 - 1947 (Box 13, Folder 48)
  - Telegrams, ca. 1943 - 1947 (Box 13, Folder 49)